const Questions=[
    {
        id:1,
      question:'Which of these React native components will be used to display the name="React Native Tutorial"?',
      option1:'View',
      option2:'Text',
      option3:'span',
      option4:'p',
      answer:'Text'
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:'Which of the following components is the optimized way to show a long list of data?',
        option1:'View',
        option2:'Scrollview',
        option3:'Safeareaview',
        option4:'Flatlist',
        answer:'Flatlist'
      },
      {
        id:3,
        question:'How do you style your React Native component?',
        option1:'Stylesheet.create',
        option2:'Stylesheet.css',
        option3:'Safeareaview',
        option4:'Flatlist',
        answer:'Stylesheet.create'
      },
      {
        id:4,
        question:'Which of the following is the correct plugin to navigate from one screen to another?',
        option1:'React Hooks',
        option2:'React Navigation',
        option3:'React Router',
        option4:'Screen',
        answer:'React Navigation'
      },
      {
        id:5,
        question:'Which of the following is the correct method(hook) to make an api call on page load?',
        option1:'useState',
        option2:'useEffect',
        option3:'useReducer',
        option4:'useSelector',
        answer:'useEffect'
      },
      {
        id:6,
        question:"Which of the following is used to make sure that your input fields don't hide behind the keyboard?",
        option1:'Keyboardavoidingview',
        option2:'Keyboardview',
        option3:'View',
        option4:'Scrollview',
        answer:'Keyboardavoidingview'
      },
      {
        id:7,
        question:" What is the use case of ActivityIndicator in React Native?",
        option1:'To display a circular loading activity',
        option2:'To display a progress bar activity',
        option3:'To open the app',
        option4:'To exit the app',
        answer:'To display a circular loading activity'
      },
      {
        id:8,
        question:" How do we detect platforms in React Native?",
        option1:'Platform.OS',
        option2:'Phone.OS',
        option3:'Dimension.OS',
        option4:'RN.OS',
        answer:'Platform.OS'
      },
      {
        id:9,
        question:"Which of the following is the correct way to store data in a local device?",
        option1:'Asyncstorage',
        option2:'Localstorage',
        option3:'Sessionstorage',
        option4:'RNStorage',
        answer:'Asyncstorage'
      },
      {
        id:10,
        question:"Which of the following comes under dangerous permission in Android?",
        option1:'Read SMS',
        option2:'Ask Location',
        option3:'Show notification',
        option4:'Internet access',
        answer:'Read SMS'
      },

  ]

  export default Questions